You'll laugh again! You'll cry again!! You'll hurl again!!!
Wayne's World 2 is a comedy, music film directed by Stephen Surjik.
A message from Jim Morrison in a dream prompts cable access TV stars Wayne and Garth
to put on a rock concert, "Waynestock," with Aerosmith as headliners.
But amid the preparations, Wayne frets that a record producer is putting the moves on his
girlfriend, Cassandra, while Garth handles the advances of mega-babe Honey Hornée.
Wayne Campbell, played by Mike Myers.
Garth Algar, played by Dana Carvey.
Bobby Cahn, played by Christopher Walken.
Cassandra Wong, played by Tia Carrere.
Milton, played by Chris Farley.
Jeff Wong, played by James Hong.
Wayne's World 2 is a 1993 American comedy film directed by Stephen Surjik and starring Mike Myers and Dana
Carvey as hosts of a public-access television cable television show in Aurora, Illinois.
The film is the sequel to Wayne's World (1992), which was itself
adapted from a sketch on NBC's Saturday Night Live.
The film explores themes of concert, rock 'n' roll,
dreams, love of one's life, talk show.
The tone is lighthearted.